{"data":[
  {
    "answer": "you can stay assured you are fine free of hiv. your results are enough. avoid multiple partners in the future \u2026",
    "answer_author": "Dr. Ayman Darrag",
    "question": "is my anti hiv test conclusive or need retest?",
    "question_text": "Is my Anti Hiv Test Conclusive or need retest?",
    "tags": [
      "hiv test"
    ],
    "url": "https://questiondoctors.com/is-my-anti-hiv-test-conclusive-or-need-retest/"
  },
  {
    "answer": "hi you are 100 % hiv free good luck",
    "answer_author": "Dr Ahmed Fawzy",
    "question": "is my anti hiv test conclusive or need retest?",
    "question_text": "Is my Anti Hiv Test Conclusive or need retest?",
    "tags": [
      "hiv test"
    ],
    "url": "https://questiondoctors.com/is-my-anti-hiv-test-conclusive-or-need-retest/"
  },
  {
    "answer": "your time slots of the tests and the final result even after 241 days is indicative of hiv- free status. so just relax. and to avoid such anxiety and fear in future just avoid multiple partners. hope this helps",
    "answer_author": "Dr.Honey",
    "question": "is my anti hiv test conclusive or need retest?",
    "question_text": "Is my Anti Hiv Test Conclusive or need retest?",
    "tags": [
      "hiv test"
    ],
    "url": "https://questiondoctors.com/is-my-anti-hiv-test-conclusive-or-need-retest/"
  },
  {
    "answer": "hi i see no labrum tear however i see acetabular rim ossifications which can cause pain on anterior aspect and lateral aspect of hip in which pain increase with hip flexion (sitting) good luck",
    "answer_author": "Dr Ahmed Fawzy",
    "question": "i have some hip pain 9 weeks. had mra image recently would welcome second opinion?",
    "question_text": "I have some hip pain 9 weeks. Had MRA image recently, would welcome second opinion?",
    "tags": [
      "magnetic resonance angiography (mra)"
    ],
    "url": "https://questiondoctors.com/i-have-some-hip-pain-9-weeks-had-mra-image-recently-would-welcome-second-opinion/"
  },
  {
    "answer": "no visible tear in labrum but obviously calcification in the acetabular rim i was treating a case like yours recently that has been alleviated by physiotherapy traction techniques mobilization and losing extra pounds.",
    "answer_author": "Dr. Ayman Darrag",
    "question": "i have some hip pain 9 weeks. had mra image recently would welcome second opinion?",
    "question_text": "I have some hip pain 9 weeks. Had MRA image recently, would welcome second opinion?",
    "tags": [
      "magnetic resonance angiography (mra)"
    ],
    "url": "https://questiondoctors.com/i-have-some-hip-pain-9-weeks-had-mra-image-recently-would-welcome-second-opinion/"
  },
  {
    "answer": "hi. it does not look like tear of labrum so i do not think presently surgery is mandatory. consult another orthopedic physician and get evaluated. physiotherapy can play an important role in alleviation of the problem. hope this helps. regards.",
    "answer_author": "Dr.Honey",
    "question": "i have some hip pain 9 weeks. had mra image recently would welcome second opinion?",
    "question_text": "I have some hip pain 9 weeks. Had MRA image recently, would welcome second opinion?",
    "tags": [
      "magnetic resonance angiography (mra)"
    ],
    "url": "https://questiondoctors.com/i-have-some-hip-pain-9-weeks-had-mra-image-recently-would-welcome-second-opinion/"
  },
  {
    "answer": "in my opinion there is no labrum tear",
    "answer_author": "Dr. D. Zluf",
    "question": "i have some hip pain 9 weeks. had mra image recently would welcome second opinion?",
    "question_text": "I have some hip pain 9 weeks. Had MRA image recently, would welcome second opinion?",
    "tags": [
      "magnetic resonance angiography (mra)"
    ],
    "url": "https://questiondoctors.com/i-have-some-hip-pain-9-weeks-had-mra-image-recently-would-welcome-second-opinion/"
  },
  {
    "answer": "in my opinion if you have something other than anxiety you should check thyroid glands and hiatal hernia possibilities then i recommend yoga breathing exercises and relaxation techniques.",
    "answer_author": "Dr. Ayman Darrag",
    "question": "i developed breathing difficulties approx 2 years ago which have worsened daily since?",
    "question_text": "I developed breathing difficulties approx 2 years ago, which have worsened daily since?",
    "tags": [
      "hyperventilation"
    ],
    "url": "https://questiondoctors.com/i-developed-breathing-difficulties-approx-2-years-ago-which-have-worsened-daily-since/"
  },
  {
    "answer": "also have barely any air to exhale",
    "answer_author": "trina",
    "question": "i developed breathing difficulties approx 2 years ago which have worsened daily since?",
    "question_text": "I developed breathing difficulties approx 2 years ago, which have worsened daily since?",
    "tags": [
      "hyperventilation"
    ],
    "url": "https://questiondoctors.com/i-developed-breathing-difficulties-approx-2-years-ago-which-have-worsened-daily-since/"
  },
  {
    "answer": "let me tell you that your main problem is anxiety up to panic attacksyou need to consult a psychotherapist as he is going to help you a lot\u2026",
    "answer_author": "Dr Masr",
    "question": "i developed breathing difficulties approx 2 years ago which have worsened daily since?",
    "question_text": "I developed breathing difficulties approx 2 years ago, which have worsened daily since?",
    "tags": [
      "hyperventilation"
    ],
    "url": "https://questiondoctors.com/i-developed-breathing-difficulties-approx-2-years-ago-which-have-worsened-daily-since/"
  },
  {
    "answer": "hi mrs trina can you try one pill of hyroxyzine 10mg ( antihistaminic) you should feel okay in 20 min if this does not help then you should switch doctors and see a psychiatrist specialist do not take more than 10mg as this is just test phase we can discuss dosage later if it helped good luck",
    "answer_author": "Dr Ahmed Fawzy",
    "question": "i developed breathing difficulties approx 2 years ago which have worsened daily since?",
    "question_text": "I developed breathing difficulties approx 2 years ago, which have worsened daily since?",
    "tags": [
      "hyperventilation"
    ],
    "url": "https://questiondoctors.com/i-developed-breathing-difficulties-approx-2-years-ago-which-have-worsened-daily-since/"
  },
  {
    "answer": "by the way if it is not anxiety and hydroxizine does not help then i recommend checking for hyperthyroidism or increased adrenal secretions both can cause shocking sensation and shallow breathing",
    "answer_author": "Dr Ahmed Fawzy",
    "question": "i developed breathing difficulties approx 2 years ago which have worsened daily since?",
    "question_text": "I developed breathing difficulties approx 2 years ago, which have worsened daily since?",
    "tags": [
      "hyperventilation"
    ],
    "url": "https://questiondoctors.com/i-developed-breathing-difficulties-approx-2-years-ago-which-have-worsened-daily-since/"
  },
  {
    "answer": "in my opinion you need to get your thyroid hormone levels checked out. symptoms of hyperthyroidism can in fact resemble those of anxiety.",
    "answer_author": "Dr. D. Zluf",
    "question": "i developed breathing difficulties approx 2 years ago which have worsened daily since?",
    "question_text": "I developed breathing difficulties approx 2 years ago, which have worsened daily since?",
    "tags": [
      "hyperventilation"
    ],
    "url": "https://questiondoctors.com/i-developed-breathing-difficulties-approx-2-years-ago-which-have-worsened-daily-since/"
  },
  {
    "answer": "hi. you can get checked for allergies as environmental allergens can cause breathing problems. also i agree that hyperthyroidism should be checked. you can once try bronchodilator sprays under supervision of your doctor and see if it can help. hope this helps.",
    "answer_author": "Dr.Honey",
    "question": "i developed breathing difficulties approx 2 years ago which have worsened daily since?",
    "question_text": "I developed breathing difficulties approx 2 years ago, which have worsened daily since?",
    "tags": [
      "hyperventilation"
    ],
    "url": "https://questiondoctors.com/i-developed-breathing-difficulties-approx-2-years-ago-which-have-worsened-daily-since/"
  },
  {
    "answer": "hi as you stated it was just after a traumatic event so the is mostly stress however to be safe do a thyroid profile to check for hypothyroidism as parasympathetic system start working few days after the traumatic event adrenaline drops normaly this is called parasympathetic overdrive if your heart rate does not improve on its own on daily bases you will have to consult both a psychiatrist and cardiologist good luck",
    "answer_author": "Dr Ahmed Fawzy",
    "question": "low resting heart rate can it be a secondary adrenal insufficiency if not what is cause?",
    "question_text": "Low resting heart rate can it be a secondary adrenal insufficiency, if not what is cause?",
    "tags": [
      "low heart rate",
      "secondary adrenal crisis",
      "secondary adrenal insufficiency"
    ],
    "url": "https://questiondoctors.com/low-resting-heart-rate-can-it-be-a-secondary-adrenal-insufficiency-if-not-what-is-cause/"
  },
  {
    "answer": "this is normal after severe stressful traumatic events no need to worry now just try to calm down for some time and it will resolve on its own. if persisted then cortisol hormone thyroid profile will be needed.",
    "answer_author": "Dr. Ayman Darrag",
    "question": "low resting heart rate can it be a secondary adrenal insufficiency if not what is cause?",
    "question_text": "Low resting heart rate can it be a secondary adrenal insufficiency, if not what is cause?",
    "tags": [
      "low heart rate",
      "secondary adrenal crisis",
      "secondary adrenal insufficiency"
    ],
    "url": "https://questiondoctors.com/low-resting-heart-rate-can-it-be-a-secondary-adrenal-insufficiency-if-not-what-is-cause/"
  },
  {
    "answer": "yes stress can cause bradycardia or reduced heart rate and as you have a recent stressful event it can be a cause. so my advise to you is to first of all relax and start doing meditation and deep breathing exercises. take nutritious and a sufficient sleep of atleast 8 hours. if at all the symptoms does not get better then consult a cardiologist and get a thorough evaluation done. hope this helps.",
    "answer_author": "Dr.Honey",
    "question": "low resting heart rate can it be a secondary adrenal insufficiency if not what is cause?",
    "question_text": "Low resting heart rate can it be a secondary adrenal insufficiency, if not what is cause?",
    "tags": [
      "low heart rate",
      "secondary adrenal crisis",
      "secondary adrenal insufficiency"
    ],
    "url": "https://questiondoctors.com/low-resting-heart-rate-can-it-be-a-secondary-adrenal-insufficiency-if-not-what-is-cause/"
  },
  {
    "answer": "if you are experiencing one of these symptoms you \u2018ll need to do furthur tests and check up if you feel dizzy or lightheaded. feel short of breath and find it harder to exercise feel tired have chest pain or a feeling that your heart is pounding or fluttering (palpitations) feel confused faintingyou already mentioned that you have one of thoses so let\u2019s do cbc thyroid profile and echo",
    "answer_author": "Dr Masr",
    "question": "low resting heart rate can it be a secondary adrenal insufficiency if not what is cause?",
    "question_text": "Low resting heart rate can it be a secondary adrenal insufficiency, if not what is cause?",
    "tags": [
      "low heart rate",
      "secondary adrenal crisis",
      "secondary adrenal insufficiency"
    ],
    "url": "https://questiondoctors.com/low-resting-heart-rate-can-it-be-a-secondary-adrenal-insufficiency-if-not-what-is-cause/"
  },
  {
    "answer": "hi my opinion i see no reason to be concerned about familial atypical mole malignant melanoma syndrome just keep up checking the moles periodically good luck",
    "answer_author": "Dr Ahmed Fawzy",
    "question": "i was recently diagnosed with an atypical mole (dysplastic nevi) please advise?",
    "question_text": "I was recently diagnosed with an Atypical Mole (Dysplastic Nevi), please advise?",
    "tags": [
      "atypical mole (dysplastic nevi)"
    ],
    "url": "https://questiondoctors.com/i-was-recently-diagnosed-with-an-atypical-mole-dysplastic-nevi-please-advise/"
  },
  {
    "answer": "hi this is normal to have such pain after catheter removal so there is nothing to worry about however pain can be due to urine concentration in which case you will need to drink lots of fluid to reduce the concentration good luck",
    "answer_author": "Dr Ahmed Fawzy",
    "question": "after reconstructive surgery i have extreme pain when i relax bladder muscles?",
    "question_text": "After reconstructive surgery, I have extreme pain when I relax bladder muscles?",
    "tags": [
      "bladder reconstructive surgery"
    ],
    "url": "https://questiondoctors.com/after-reconstructive-surgery-i-have-extreme-pain-when-i-relax-bladder-muscles/"
  },
  {
    "answer": "until the to moment there is no need to worry about that however keep monitoring any abnormal changes in the moles like change in size or bleeding.",
    "answer_author": "Dr. Ayman Darrag",
    "question": "i was recently diagnosed with an atypical mole (dysplastic nevi) please advise?",
    "question_text": "I was recently diagnosed with an Atypical Mole (Dysplastic Nevi), please advise?",
    "tags": [
      "atypical mole (dysplastic nevi)"
    ],
    "url": "https://questiondoctors.com/i-was-recently-diagnosed-with-an-atypical-mole-dysplastic-nevi-please-advise/"
  },
  {
    "answer": "well all moles are not cancerous so you need not to worry about it as most of your neck are totally harmless. secondly every information on internet is not related to your symptoms so no need to relate everything to your own self and get stressed. you are rightly advised as there is nothing to worry so just relax. your symptoms are not related to fammms. hope this helps.",
    "answer_author": "Dr.Honey",
    "question": "i was recently diagnosed with an atypical mole (dysplastic nevi) please advise?",
    "question_text": "I was recently diagnosed with an Atypical Mole (Dysplastic Nevi), please advise?",
    "tags": [
      "atypical mole (dysplastic nevi)"
    ],
    "url": "https://questiondoctors.com/i-was-recently-diagnosed-with-an-atypical-mole-dysplastic-nevi-please-advise/"
  },
  {
    "answer": "no if it\u2019s degree is such severe and agonizing please describe the pain for me and how long does the pain takes place what pain killers are you taking. have you done any follow-up tests",
    "answer_author": "Dr Masr",
    "question": "after reconstructive surgery i have extreme pain when i relax bladder muscles?",
    "question_text": "After reconstructive surgery, I have extreme pain when I relax bladder muscles?",
    "tags": [
      "bladder reconstructive surgery"
    ],
    "url": "https://questiondoctors.com/after-reconstructive-surgery-i-have-extreme-pain-when-i-relax-bladder-muscles/"
  },
  {
    "answer": "this is very common no worries but drink plenty of water.",
    "answer_author": "Dr. Ayman Darrag",
    "question": "after reconstructive surgery i have extreme pain when i relax bladder muscles?",
    "question_text": "After reconstructive surgery, I have extreme pain when I relax bladder muscles?",
    "tags": [
      "bladder reconstructive surgery"
    ],
    "url": "https://questiondoctors.com/after-reconstructive-surgery-i-have-extreme-pain-when-i-relax-bladder-muscles/"
  },
  {
    "answer": "hi. yes the pain is common. you should drink plenty of water to let the urine be dilute and will ease in evacuation. can you tell which painkillers are you taking? regards.",
    "answer_author": "Dr.Honey",
    "question": "after reconstructive surgery i have extreme pain when i relax bladder muscles?",
    "question_text": "After reconstructive surgery, I have extreme pain when I relax bladder muscles?",
    "tags": [
      "bladder reconstructive surgery"
    ],
    "url": "https://questiondoctors.com/after-reconstructive-surgery-i-have-extreme-pain-when-i-relax-bladder-muscles/"
  },
  {
    "answer": "well tecfidera can cause loss of appetite if you experienced so then it is normal to suffer weight loss while ms is commonly causing weight gain but in few cases muscle mass loss can occur if you have gi problems or absorption disorder exercising and activity and proper diet can help you avoid this.",
    "answer_author": "Dr. Ayman Darrag",
    "question": "i\u2019ve been diagnosed with relapsing-remitting multiple sclerosis (rrms) losing weight can it be lyme disease?",
    "question_text": "I\u2019ve been diagnosed with Relapsing-Remitting Multiple Sclerosis (RRMS), losing weight can it be Lyme Disease?",
    "tags": [
      "relapsing-remitting multiple sclerosis (rrms)"
    ],
    "url": "https://questiondoctors.com/ive-been-diagnosed-with-relapsing-remitting-multiple-sclerosis-rrms-losing-weight-can-it-be-lyme-disease/"
  },
  {
    "answer": "hi tecfidera is the main cause of weight lose if you want confirm if it is ms or not then you should do a spinal tap good luck",
    "answer_author": "Dr Ahmed Fawzy",
    "question": "i\u2019ve been diagnosed with relapsing-remitting multiple sclerosis (rrms) losing weight can it be lyme disease?",
    "question_text": "I\u2019ve been diagnosed with Relapsing-Remitting Multiple Sclerosis (RRMS), losing weight can it be Lyme Disease?",
    "tags": [
      "relapsing-remitting multiple sclerosis (rrms)"
    ],
    "url": "https://questiondoctors.com/ive-been-diagnosed-with-relapsing-remitting-multiple-sclerosis-rrms-losing-weight-can-it-be-lyme-disease/"
  },
  {
    "answer": "also tecfidera can cause lyme disease like symptoms",
    "answer_author": "Dr Ahmed Fawzy",
    "question": "i\u2019ve been diagnosed with relapsing-remitting multiple sclerosis (rrms) losing weight can it be lyme disease?",
    "question_text": "I\u2019ve been diagnosed with Relapsing-Remitting Multiple Sclerosis (RRMS), losing weight can it be Lyme Disease?",
    "tags": [
      "relapsing-remitting multiple sclerosis (rrms)"
    ],
    "url": "https://questiondoctors.com/ive-been-diagnosed-with-relapsing-remitting-multiple-sclerosis-rrms-losing-weight-can-it-be-lyme-disease/"
  },
  {
    "answer": "tecfidera mostly cause weight loss but not in a unilateral mannar there is something else causing you this may be the decrease in the usage of this side due to your condition. i recommend you to be reassessed again",
    "answer_author": "Dr Masr",
    "question": "i\u2019ve been diagnosed with relapsing-remitting multiple sclerosis (rrms) losing weight can it be lyme disease?",
    "question_text": "I\u2019ve been diagnosed with Relapsing-Remitting Multiple Sclerosis (RRMS), losing weight can it be Lyme Disease?",
    "tags": [
      "relapsing-remitting multiple sclerosis (rrms)"
    ],
    "url": "https://questiondoctors.com/ive-been-diagnosed-with-relapsing-remitting-multiple-sclerosis-rrms-losing-weight-can-it-be-lyme-disease/"
  },
  {
    "answer": "hi regarding the skin sinking on left side it is normal as less internal components are on the left side (only spleen) and your myalgic encephalomyelitis is weakening your respiratory muscles leaving sinking between the ribs well only effective way to lose weight if you can not exercise is to keep fats in your diet and have carbohydrates only in first hour after you wake up i know it sounds weird as eating fats to lose weight but scientificly speaking it\u2019s correct good luck",
    "answer_author": "Dr Ahmed Fawzy",
    "question": "i have me myalgic encephalomyelitis and finding it impossible to lose weight?",
    "question_text": "I have ME Myalgic Encephalomyelitis and finding it impossible to lose weight?",
    "tags": [
      "myalgic encephalomyelitis"
    ],
    "url": "https://questiondoctors.com/i-have-me-myalgic-encephalomyelitis-and-finding-it-impossible-to-lose-weight/"
  },
  {
    "answer": "hi. well myalgic encephalopathy is a rare disorder and as its name suggests it being chronic fatigue\u200b syndrome doing workout for weight loss can further worsen the symptoms. you will have to manage a proper diet as it is not the excuse that you can take. this will even help in managing weight. also physical therapy should be restarted under supervision of your physician as it helps in gradually regaining strength too. this process is known as graded exercise therapy. proper sleep is also helpful in maintaining a good metabolism also. hope this helps. regards.",
    "answer_author": "Dr.Honey",
    "question": "i have me myalgic encephalomyelitis and finding it impossible to lose weight?",
    "question_text": "I have ME Myalgic Encephalomyelitis and finding it impossible to lose weight?",
    "tags": [
      "myalgic encephalomyelitis"
    ],
    "url": "https://questiondoctors.com/i-have-me-myalgic-encephalomyelitis-and-finding-it-impossible-to-lose-weight/"
  },
  {
    "answer": "you can try very simple exercises low intensity with yoga you may also use local lipolysis techniques to get rid of the localized central fat.",
    "answer_author": "Dr. Ayman Darrag",
    "question": "i have me myalgic encephalomyelitis and finding it impossible to lose weight?",
    "question_text": "I have ME Myalgic Encephalomyelitis and finding it impossible to lose weight?",
    "tags": [
      "myalgic encephalomyelitis"
    ],
    "url": "https://questiondoctors.com/i-have-me-myalgic-encephalomyelitis-and-finding-it-impossible-to-lose-weight/"
  },
  {
    "answer": "hi my opinion stay on your azulfidine if it is keeping g things under control unless your doctor wana try diet instead of keeping you on medications as some inflammatory bowel disease can simply be controlled with diet so you need to demand an explanation of why he wants to redo the endoscopy good luck",
    "answer_author": "Dr Ahmed Fawzy",
    "question": "i am diagnosed with inflammatory bowel disease unclassified (ibdu) don\u2019t want to stop treatment for another colonoscopy? now have to go for another scope",
    "question_text": "I AM Diagnosed with Inflammatory bowel disease unclassified (IBDU) don\u2019t want to stop treatment for another colonoscopy?now have to go for another scope",
    "tags": [
      "inflammatory bowel disease unclassified (ibdu)"
    ],
    "url": "https://questiondoctors.com/i-am-diagnosed-with-inflammatory-bowel-disease-unclassified-ibdu-dont-want-to-stop-treatment-for-another-colonoscopynow-have-to-go-for-another-scope/"
  },
  {
    "answer": "in my opinion having a colonoscopy in the presence of a probability if ulcerative colitis is going to help understanding the problem closely and getting an appropriate management plan. however if symptoms is improving with current treatment it might not be necessary at this time.",
    "answer_author": "Dr. Ayman Darrag",
    "question": "i am diagnosed with inflammatory bowel disease unclassified (ibdu) don\u2019t want to stop treatment for another colonoscopy? now have to go for another scope",
    "question_text": "I AM Diagnosed with Inflammatory bowel disease unclassified (IBDU) don\u2019t want to stop treatment for another colonoscopy?now have to go for another scope",
    "tags": [
      "inflammatory bowel disease unclassified (ibdu)"
    ],
    "url": "https://questiondoctors.com/i-am-diagnosed-with-inflammatory-bowel-disease-unclassified-ibdu-dont-want-to-stop-treatment-for-another-colonoscopynow-have-to-go-for-another-scope/"
  },
  {
    "answer": "well individuals with low igg levels tend to get infection more frequently as igg antibodies are responsible for preventing infection in the body. so in case of igg deficiency the body tend to get frequent infection. so you should consult an immunologist and get evaluated and igg replacement therapy can help in reducing the frequency of infection. in case if you get infection you should immediately get a proper treatment to avoid worsening. hope this helps. regards.",
    "answer_author": "Dr.Honey",
    "question": "my immune system is deficient in the 1gg3 classification please advise?",
    "question_text": "My immune system is deficient in the 1gG3 classification, please advise?",
    "tags": [
      "immune system deficiency"
    ],
    "url": "https://questiondoctors.com/my-immune-system-is-deficient-in-the-1gg3-classification-please-advise/"
  },
  {
    "answer": "your immune deficiency condition makes you more liable to experience more frequent infections discuss with your specialist the options of infection control life style modifications and even prophylactic antibiotics if neededseek the er help if you find yourself with obvious increase in the work of breathing high grade fever above 38 shortness of breathing not responding to treatment may be you need a specific regimen of cortisone and beta 2 agonist to relieve your asthma symptoms as well you need a team of both immunologist and pulmonologistgood luck",
    "answer_author": "Dr Masr",
    "question": "my immune system is deficient in the 1gg3 classification please advise?",
    "question_text": "My immune system is deficient in the 1gG3 classification, please advise?",
    "tags": [
      "immune system deficiency"
    ],
    "url": "https://questiondoctors.com/my-immune-system-is-deficient-in-the-1gg3-classification-please-advise/"
  },
  {
    "answer": "your problem is a chronic one so er can be sought only in cases of severe breathing difficulty and wheezing of chest however you need to see an immunologist to get a good treatment plan for improving your immunity with vitamins and life style modification also a pulmonologist will prescribe b2 agonist and corticosteroid to control the symptoms also you can get acetylecysteine effervescent to reduce the viscosity of the secretions drink plenty of water and warm drinks ginger can help you also avoid useless intake of antibiotics as this will destroy your immunity.",
    "answer_author": "Dr. Ayman Darrag",
    "question": "my immune system is deficient in the 1gg3 classification please advise?",
    "question_text": "My immune system is deficient in the 1gG3 classification, please advise?",
    "tags": [
      "immune system deficiency"
    ],
    "url": "https://questiondoctors.com/my-immune-system-is-deficient-in-the-1gg3-classification-please-advise/"
  },
  {
    "answer": "hi if you have blood in cough or if you feel unable to breath while lying down then you need to go to er immediately on the long run you will need igg replacement therapy good luck",
    "answer_author": "Dr Ahmed Fawzy",
    "question": "my immune system is deficient in the 1gg3 classification please advise?",
    "question_text": "My immune system is deficient in the 1gG3 classification, please advise?",
    "tags": [
      "immune system deficiency"
    ],
    "url": "https://questiondoctors.com/my-immune-system-is-deficient-in-the-1gg3-classification-please-advise/"
  },
  {
    "answer": "hi i am physical therapist and your lumber lordosis can be fixed and restored main idea is to restore pelvic tilt to a posterior tilt position this can be achieved by stretching back muscles testis femoris and iliopsoas muscles strengthening abdominal and hamstrings also if your physical therapist can achieve normal ankle dorsi flexion 5 to 10 degree then his treatment can be permanent protection from recurrence good luck",
    "answer_author": "Dr Ahmed Fawzy",
    "question": "i have lordosis of back spine need second opinion?",
    "question_text": "I have Lordosis of back spine, need second opinion?",
    "tags": [
      "lordosis"
    ],
    "url": "https://questiondoctors.com/i-have-lordosis-of-back-spine-need-second-opinion/"
  },
  {
    "answer": "lordosis can be very well improved and posture can be restored with the help of physiotherapy and exercises like hip flexor stretch lower back stretch twisting crunch abdominal crunch bridge etc can be helpful. but you should get it done by an expert physiotherapist under supervision of your doctor. hope this helps.",
    "answer_author": "Dr.Honey",
    "question": "i have lordosis of back spine need second opinion?",
    "question_text": "I have Lordosis of back spine, need second opinion?",
    "tags": [
      "lordosis"
    ],
    "url": "https://questiondoctors.com/i-have-lordosis-of-back-spine-need-second-opinion/"
  },
  {
    "answer": "that\u2019s totally a wrong information. however it depends on its degree consult another physiotherapist use a backbrace i believe can help you as well if you have done mri please upload to help you better",
    "answer_author": "Dr Masr",
    "question": "i have lordosis of back spine need second opinion?",
    "question_text": "I have Lordosis of back spine, need second opinion?",
    "tags": [
      "lordosis"
    ],
    "url": "https://questiondoctors.com/i-have-lordosis-of-back-spine-need-second-opinion/"
  },
  {
    "answer": "hi i need to see the mri before i can give you a perfect answer however if it was tb then he will need both tb treatment + surgery as neglected to must be corrected later by surgery conclusion is that surgery is a must if it is indeed tb good luck",
    "answer_author": "Dr Ahmed Fawzy",
    "question": "bone tuberculosis (tb) diagnosis cannot be confirmed do we opt for surgery or tb medication?",
    "question_text": "Bone Tuberculosis (TB) Diagnosis  cannot be confirmed, do we opt for surgery or TB medication?",
    "tags": [
      "bone ttberculosis (tb) diagnosis"
    ],
    "url": "https://questiondoctors.com/bone-tuberculosis-tb-diagnosis-cannot-be-confirmed-do-we-opt-for-surgery-or-tb-medication/"
  },
  {
    "answer": "you need to do mantoux tuberculin skin test and blood culture to confirm the diagnosis aspiration is gonna be diagnostic as well",
    "answer_author": "Dr Masr",
    "question": "bone tuberculosis (tb) diagnosis cannot be confirmed do we opt for surgery or tb medication?",
    "question_text": "Bone Tuberculosis (TB) Diagnosis  cannot be confirmed, do we opt for surgery or TB medication?",
    "tags": [
      "bone ttberculosis (tb) diagnosis"
    ],
    "url": "https://questiondoctors.com/bone-tuberculosis-tb-diagnosis-cannot-be-confirmed-do-we-opt-for-surgery-or-tb-medication/"
  },
  {
    "answer": "you need to consider polymerase chain reaction for diagnosis as early as possible then medical treatment should be followed mostly 80-90%of cases respond to anti tb drugs and surgical treatment is necessary only in case of complications.",
    "answer_author": "Dr. Ayman Darrag",
    "question": "bone tuberculosis (tb) diagnosis cannot be confirmed do we opt for surgery or tb medication?",
    "question_text": "Bone Tuberculosis (TB) Diagnosis  cannot be confirmed, do we opt for surgery or TB medication?",
    "tags": [
      "bone ttberculosis (tb) diagnosis"
    ],
    "url": "https://questiondoctors.com/bone-tuberculosis-tb-diagnosis-cannot-be-confirmed-do-we-opt-for-surgery-or-tb-medication/"
  },
  {
    "answer": "this may be alopecia areata you need to get a scalp biopsy done to rule out times capitis crp ana tests.",
    "answer_author": "Dr. Ayman Darrag",
    "question": "sudden bald spot on top of head please advise?",
    "question_text": "Sudden bald spot on top of head, please advise?",
    "tags": [
      "sudden balding"
    ],
    "url": "https://questiondoctors.com/sudden-bald-spot-on-top-of-head-please-advise/"
  },
  {
    "answer": "hi this seems like alopecia the there are multiple treatments not all work for everyone you can start by trying corticosteroids minoxidil good luck",
    "answer_author": "Dr Ahmed Fawzy",
    "question": "sudden bald spot on top of head please advise?",
    "question_text": "Sudden bald spot on top of head, please advise?",
    "tags": [
      "sudden balding"
    ],
    "url": "https://questiondoctors.com/sudden-bald-spot-on-top-of-head-please-advise/"
  },
  {
    "answer": "it is looking like androgenic aloepecia that is male pattern baldness. i would like to know that are you taking any medication? is any one else in family like your father or grandfather had baldness? are you in any long standing stressful situation? do you have itching in scalp or any white flakes over the scalp? please write back so that i can advise you how to proceed for treatment. regards.",
    "answer_author": "Dr.Honey",
    "question": "sudden bald spot on top of head please advise?",
    "question_text": "Sudden bald spot on top of head, please advise?",
    "tags": [
      "sudden balding"
    ],
    "url": "https://questiondoctors.com/sudden-bald-spot-on-top-of-head-please-advise/"
  },
  {
    "answer": "hi. it looks like nerve related pain or muscle pull. you need to get it clinically examined and if a confirmation is needed mri scan can be done\u200b. for now take painkillers like ibuprofen for pain relief if needed. hope this helps. regards.",
    "answer_author": "Dr.Honey",
    "question": "after staph infection i have been getting pressure and sharp or dull throbbing pain in my upper left leg?",
    "question_text": "After staph infection, I have been getting pressure and sharp or dull throbbing pain in my upper left leg?",
    "tags": [
      "staph infection"
    ],
    "url": "https://questiondoctors.com/after-staph-infection-i-have-been-getting-pressure-and-sharp-or-dull-throbbing-pain-in-my-upper-left-leg/"
  },
  {
    "answer": "you are describing something different this is most probably joint/muscle related have you done mri or xray of hip joint?",
    "answer_author": "Dr. Ayman Darrag",
    "question": "after staph infection i have been getting pressure and sharp or dull throbbing pain in my upper left leg?",
    "question_text": "After staph infection, I have been getting pressure and sharp or dull throbbing pain in my upper left leg?",
    "tags": [
      "staph infection"
    ],
    "url": "https://questiondoctors.com/after-staph-infection-i-have-been-getting-pressure-and-sharp-or-dull-throbbing-pain-in-my-upper-left-leg/"
  },
  {
    "answer": "have you done neonatal ultrasound sound? placenta beats i think he means the mother\u2019s beats where the blood is successfully perfused across the placenta",
    "answer_author": "Dr Masr",
    "question": "i was told yesterday that my baby has no heart rate at 38 weeks and 3 days?",
    "question_text": "I was told yesterday that my baby has no heart rate at 38 weeks and 3 days?",
    "tags": [
      "no babies heart rate"
    ],
    "url": "https://questiondoctors.com/i-was-told-yesterday-that-my-baby-has-no-heart-rate-at-38-weeks-and-3-days/"
  },
  {
    "answer": "hi sorry but there is no chance your baby\u2019s heart rate is 120 you should go on with the early delivery sorry",
    "answer_author": "Dr Ahmed Fawzy",
    "question": "i was told yesterday that my baby has no heart rate at 38 weeks and 3 days?",
    "question_text": "I was told yesterday that my baby has no heart rate at 38 weeks and 3 days?",
    "tags": [
      "no babies heart rate"
    ],
    "url": "https://questiondoctors.com/i-was-told-yesterday-that-my-baby-has-no-heart-rate-at-38-weeks-and-3-days/"
  },
  {
    "answer": "i am so sorry to hear about the problem but if you doubt then before you proceed for delivery you can once again reconfirm by getting a fetal ultrasound done. if unfortunately there is no heartbeat then there is no other option then delivering the baby as soon as possible. be strong.",
    "answer_author": "Dr.Honey",
    "question": "i was told yesterday that my baby has no heart rate at 38 weeks and 3 days?",
    "question_text": "I was told yesterday that my baby has no heart rate at 38 weeks and 3 days?",
    "tags": [
      "no babies heart rate"
    ],
    "url": "https://questiondoctors.com/i-was-told-yesterday-that-my-baby-has-no-heart-rate-at-38-weeks-and-3-days/"
  },
  {
    "answer": "you need to check why this happened and try to fix in the upcoming pregnancies",
    "answer_author": "Dr Masr",
    "question": "i was told yesterday that my baby has no heart rate at 38 weeks and 3 days?",
    "question_text": "I was told yesterday that my baby has no heart rate at 38 weeks and 3 days?",
    "tags": [
      "no babies heart rate"
    ],
    "url": "https://questiondoctors.com/i-was-told-yesterday-that-my-baby-has-no-heart-rate-at-38-weeks-and-3-days/"
  },
  {
    "answer": "sorry about that but you have to abort get examined thereafter to know the cause and treat the problem in the next time.",
    "answer_author": "Dr. Ayman Darrag",
    "question": "i was told yesterday that my baby has no heart rate at 38 weeks and 3 days?",
    "question_text": "I was told yesterday that my baby has no heart rate at 38 weeks and 3 days?",
    "tags": [
      "no babies heart rate"
    ],
    "url": "https://questiondoctors.com/i-was-told-yesterday-that-my-baby-has-no-heart-rate-at-38-weeks-and-3-days/"
  },
  {
    "answer": "was there a fetal ultrasound done? you can ask your doctor to double check with another ultrasound. so you can rest assured.",
    "answer_author": "Dr. D. Zluf",
    "question": "i was told yesterday that my baby has no heart rate at 38 weeks and 3 days?",
    "question_text": "I was told yesterday that my baby has no heart rate at 38 weeks and 3 days?",
    "tags": [
      "no babies heart rate"
    ],
    "url": "https://questiondoctors.com/i-was-told-yesterday-that-my-baby-has-no-heart-rate-at-38-weeks-and-3-days/"
  },
  {
    "answer": "hi this is probably swollen lymph nodes from sacroidosis also if she is on corticosteroids then she can have pumps like this all over if i am here doctor i would not focus on this instead i would focus on the bigger issues good luck",
    "answer_author": "Dr Ahmed Fawzy",
    "question": "my mom has kidney failure diabetes sarcoidosis heart failure she now has these big knots why?",
    "question_text": "My mom has, kidney failure diabetes sarcoidosis heart failure  she now has these big knots why?",
    "tags": [
      "sarcoidosis"
    ],
    "url": "https://questiondoctors.com/my-mom-has-kidney-failure-diabetes-sarcoidosis-heart-failure-she-now-has-these-big-knots-why/"
  },
  {
    "answer": "hi the brown blessings (coagulated) are probably side effects from contraceptive injection cervix bleeding would be the pink ones so i see no reason to worry follow up with your gynecologist good luck",
    "answer_author": "Dr Ahmed Fawzy",
    "question": "i had cold coagulation for (cin) cervical intraepithelial neoplasia i have bleeding since that day?",
    "question_text": "I had cold coagulation for (cin) cervical intraepithelial neoplasia, I have bleeding since that day?",
    "tags": [
      "cervical intraepithelial neoplasia",
      "cold coagulation for cin"
    ],
    "url": "https://questiondoctors.com/i-had-cold-coagulation-for-cin-cervical-intraepithelial-neoplasia-i-have-bleeding-since-that-day/"
  },
  {
    "answer": "most probably these are because of corticosteroids however not the matter of concern.",
    "answer_author": "Dr. Ayman Darrag",
    "question": "my mom has kidney failure diabetes sarcoidosis heart failure she now has these big knots why?",
    "question_text": "My mom has, kidney failure diabetes sarcoidosis heart failure  she now has these big knots why?",
    "tags": [
      "sarcoidosis"
    ],
    "url": "https://questiondoctors.com/my-mom-has-kidney-failure-diabetes-sarcoidosis-heart-failure-she-now-has-these-big-knots-why/"
  },
  {
    "answer": "hi. sarcoidosis can cause formation of lumps or granulomas or it can involve the lymph nodes. if she has any symptoms like pain then painkillers\u200b can help but should be taken only under consent with her doctor as she already has renal failure. also a biopsy can be do e if further confirmation is needed. can you also tell that these bumps appeared suddenly or gradually? are they painful? please revert back. regards.",
    "answer_author": "Dr.Honey",
    "question": "my mom has kidney failure diabetes sarcoidosis heart failure she now has these big knots why?",
    "question_text": "My mom has, kidney failure diabetes sarcoidosis heart failure  she now has these big knots why?",
    "tags": [
      "sarcoidosis"
    ],
    "url": "https://questiondoctors.com/my-mom-has-kidney-failure-diabetes-sarcoidosis-heart-failure-she-now-has-these-big-knots-why/"
  },
  {
    "answer": "these side effects are normal and commom after such procedures but it is recommended to check your cbc for a possible anaemia due to bleeding and get a follow up with your gynacologist.",
    "answer_author": "Dr. Ayman Darrag",
    "question": "i had cold coagulation for (cin) cervical intraepithelial neoplasia i have bleeding since that day?",
    "question_text": "I had cold coagulation for (cin) cervical intraepithelial neoplasia, I have bleeding since that day?",
    "tags": [
      "cervical intraepithelial neoplasia",
      "cold coagulation for cin"
    ],
    "url": "https://questiondoctors.com/i-had-cold-coagulation-for-cin-cervical-intraepithelial-neoplasia-i-have-bleeding-since-that-day/"
  },
  {
    "answer": "bleeding after cold coagulation can occur for about a maximum of 2-3 weeks approximately but it generally does not extend for more than this time. but if the bleeding is still occuring you should immediately consult your treating physician and get evaluated for checking out any bleeding vessels or other causes. hope this helps.",
    "answer_author": "Dr.Honey",
    "question": "i had cold coagulation for (cin) cervical intraepithelial neoplasia i have bleeding since that day?",
    "question_text": "I had cold coagulation for (cin) cervical intraepithelial neoplasia, I have bleeding since that day?",
    "tags": [
      "cervical intraepithelial neoplasia",
      "cold coagulation for cin"
    ],
    "url": "https://questiondoctors.com/i-had-cold-coagulation-for-cin-cervical-intraepithelial-neoplasia-i-have-bleeding-since-that-day/"
  },
  {
    "answer": "it\u2019s a normal sequelle after the coagulation and the treatment that you are taking don\u2019t panic you just need to follow up with your gynecologist and to do fbc",
    "answer_author": "Dr Masr",
    "question": "i had cold coagulation for (cin) cervical intraepithelial neoplasia i have bleeding since that day?",
    "question_text": "I had cold coagulation for (cin) cervical intraepithelial neoplasia, I have bleeding since that day?",
    "tags": [
      "cervical intraepithelial neoplasia",
      "cold coagulation for cin"
    ],
    "url": "https://questiondoctors.com/i-had-cold-coagulation-for-cin-cervical-intraepithelial-neoplasia-i-have-bleeding-since-that-day/"
  },
  {
    "answer": "ecg brain mri and echo. should be done asapwhat medications is he taking? tell me more about the affected part in his body in the previous stroke want happened and how did you manage it plz",
    "answer_author": "Dr Masr",
    "question": "my husband is 42y/o hx. of stroke 1 year ago. he awakened yesterday complaining of heaviness to his left arm?",
    "question_text": "My husband is 42y/o Hx. of stroke 1 year ago.  He awakened yesterday complaining of heaviness to his left arm?",
    "tags": [
      "stroke"
    ],
    "url": "https://questiondoctors.com/my-husband-is-42yo-hx-of-stroke-1-year-ago-he-awakened-yesterday-complaining-of-heaviness-to-his-left-arm/"
  },
  {
    "answer": "hi this is not common set back go to the er and do a brain mri as soon as possible good luck",
    "answer_author": "Dr Ahmed Fawzy",
    "question": "my husband is 42y/o hx. of stroke 1 year ago. he awakened yesterday complaining of heaviness to his left arm?",
    "question_text": "My husband is 42y/o Hx. of stroke 1 year ago.  He awakened yesterday complaining of heaviness to his left arm?",
    "tags": [
      "stroke"
    ],
    "url": "https://questiondoctors.com/my-husband-is-42yo-hx-of-stroke-1-year-ago-he-awakened-yesterday-complaining-of-heaviness-to-his-left-arm/"
  },
  {
    "answer": "that\u2019s an emergency it can be a tia warning so you need to get inr test mri for brain. clinical evaluation is not reliable in some cases.",
    "answer_author": "Dr. Ayman Darrag",
    "question": "my husband is 42y/o hx. of stroke 1 year ago. he awakened yesterday complaining of heaviness to his left arm?",
    "question_text": "My husband is 42y/o Hx. of stroke 1 year ago.  He awakened yesterday complaining of heaviness to his left arm?",
    "tags": [
      "stroke"
    ],
    "url": "https://questiondoctors.com/my-husband-is-42yo-hx-of-stroke-1-year-ago-he-awakened-yesterday-complaining-of-heaviness-to-his-left-arm/"
  },
  {
    "answer": "the symptoms looks like a medical emergency. consult an emergency room. let them do investigations like mri scan done for a quick diagnosis. other investigation can follow once management is initiated. hope this helps.",
    "answer_author": "Dr.Honey",
    "question": "my husband is 42y/o hx. of stroke 1 year ago. he awakened yesterday complaining of heaviness to his left arm?",
    "question_text": "My husband is 42y/o Hx. of stroke 1 year ago.  He awakened yesterday complaining of heaviness to his left arm?",
    "tags": [
      "stroke"
    ],
    "url": "https://questiondoctors.com/my-husband-is-42yo-hx-of-stroke-1-year-ago-he-awakened-yesterday-complaining-of-heaviness-to-his-left-arm/"
  },
  {
    "answer": "you will need to go to er for urgent tests.",
    "answer_author": "Dr. D. Zluf",
    "question": "my husband is 42y/o hx. of stroke 1 year ago. he awakened yesterday complaining of heaviness to his left arm?",
    "question_text": "My husband is 42y/o Hx. of stroke 1 year ago.  He awakened yesterday complaining of heaviness to his left arm?",
    "tags": [
      "stroke"
    ],
    "url": "https://questiondoctors.com/my-husband-is-42yo-hx-of-stroke-1-year-ago-he-awakened-yesterday-complaining-of-heaviness-to-his-left-arm/"
  },
  {
    "answer": "hi it sounds like you have psos i need to know what drugs you tried and do an ultrasound to check for cysts hope to hear from you soon good luck",
    "answer_author": "Dr Ahmed Fawzy",
    "question": "i have irregular periods and i am trying to get pregnant?",
    "question_text": "I have Irregular periods and I am trying to get pregnant?",
    "tags": [
      "irregular periods pregnancy"
    ],
    "url": "https://questiondoctors.com/i-have-irregular-periods-and-i-am-trying-to-get-pregnant/"
  },
  {
    "answer": "hi unfortunately your only option would be surgical if your collar bone is shorter on one side the the other good luck",
    "answer_author": "Dr Ahmed Fawzy",
    "question": "i broke my collarbone back in 2009 my chest seems to have become a bit deformed since the incident?",
    "question_text": "I broke my collarbone back in 2009, my chest seems to have become a bit deformed since the incident?",
    "tags": [
      "spine deformation"
    ],
    "url": "https://questiondoctors.com/i-broke-my-collarbone-back-in-2009-my-chest-seems-to-have-become-a-bit-deformed-since-the-incident/"
  },
  {
    "answer": "i need more details about your history your age and have you ever been pregnant before? did you get any usg done to evaluate your ovaries for pcos and ovulation? hormonal tests? please let me know so i can guide you.",
    "answer_author": "Dr. Ayman Darrag",
    "question": "i have irregular periods and i am trying to get pregnant?",
    "question_text": "I have Irregular periods and I am trying to get pregnant?",
    "tags": [
      "irregular periods pregnancy"
    ],
    "url": "https://questiondoctors.com/i-have-irregular-periods-and-i-am-trying-to-get-pregnant/"
  },
  {
    "answer": "good day and thank you for your question. irregular periods can be caused by numerous issues such as excessive and prolonged dieting and/or exercising diabetes thyroid dysfunction endometriosis and ovarian cysts. the best option would be to consult with your primary care doctor so that these issues can be addressed and/or investigated further. the frequent urination can be caused by recurrent urinary tract infections so this problem also needs to be ruled out or managed appropriately.",
    "answer_author": "Spiros Theocharous",
    "question": "i have irregular periods and i am trying to get pregnant?",
    "question_text": "I have Irregular periods and I am trying to get pregnant?",
    "tags": [
      "irregular periods pregnancy"
    ],
    "url": "https://questiondoctors.com/i-have-irregular-periods-and-i-am-trying-to-get-pregnant/"
  },
  {
    "answer": "hi\u2026. thanks for the query. there can be problem associated with the ovaries like cysts that can commonly cause problem with ovulation and cause difficulty in getting pregnant. i would suggest you to first of all consult a gynaecologist and get evaluated and get an infertility panel done along with a pelvic ultrasound for ruling out the cause. once the cause is ruled out treatment can be done accordingly. hope this helps. regards.",
    "answer_author": "Dr.Honey",
    "question": "i have irregular periods and i am trying to get pregnant?",
    "question_text": "I have Irregular periods and I am trying to get pregnant?",
    "tags": [
      "irregular periods pregnancy"
    ],
    "url": "https://questiondoctors.com/i-have-irregular-periods-and-i-am-trying-to-get-pregnant/"
  },
  {
    "answer": "the causes can be varied. you will need to provide more information profile and medications. in my opinion you will need to proceed with a thyroid check and hormonal profile",
    "answer_author": "Dr. D. Zluf",
    "question": "i have irregular periods and i am trying to get pregnant?",
    "question_text": "I have Irregular periods and I am trying to get pregnant?",
    "tags": [
      "irregular periods pregnancy"
    ],
    "url": "https://questiondoctors.com/i-have-irregular-periods-and-i-am-trying-to-get-pregnant/"
  },
  {
    "answer": "hi. although your explanation is pointing towards getting surgical correction as it looks. like displacement and malunion of bone bit still before i can give a more precise advise i would like to see your x-ray to rule out the exact problem. hope this helps. regards.",
    "answer_author": "Dr.Honey",
    "question": "i broke my collarbone back in 2009 my chest seems to have become a bit deformed since the incident?",
    "question_text": "I broke my collarbone back in 2009, my chest seems to have become a bit deformed since the incident?",
    "tags": [
      "spine deformation"
    ],
    "url": "https://questiondoctors.com/i-broke-my-collarbone-back-in-2009-my-chest-seems-to-have-become-a-bit-deformed-since-the-incident/"
  },
  {
    "answer": "it is my opinion that in your case surgery is the best option.",
    "answer_author": "Dr. D. Zluf",
    "question": "i broke my collarbone back in 2009 my chest seems to have become a bit deformed since the incident?",
    "question_text": "I broke my collarbone back in 2009, my chest seems to have become a bit deformed since the incident?",
    "tags": [
      "spine deformation"
    ],
    "url": "https://questiondoctors.com/i-broke-my-collarbone-back-in-2009-my-chest-seems-to-have-become-a-bit-deformed-since-the-incident/"
  },
  {
    "answer": "most probably you are suffering pelvic inflammatory disease with or without ibs you will need to get pelvic examination pelvic usg urine analysis to check for any infection.",
    "answer_author": "Dr. Ayman Darrag",
    "question": "i have a burning pain in pelvic lower abdomen & intestines?",
    "question_text": "I have a burning pain in pelvic, lower abdomen & intestines?",
    "tags": [
      "lower abdomen"
    ],
    "url": "https://questiondoctors.com/i-have-a-burning-pain-in-pelvic-lower-abdomen-intestines/"
  },
  {
    "answer": "it looks like pelvic inflammation also known as pelvic inflammatory disease. you should get a pelvic ultrasound done and also get a colonoscopy done to check your digestive tract. a cbc should also be done. hope this helps. regards.",
    "answer_author": "Dr.Honey",
    "question": "i have a burning pain in pelvic lower abdomen & intestines?",
    "question_text": "I have a burning pain in pelvic, lower abdomen & intestines?",
    "tags": [
      "lower abdomen"
    ],
    "url": "https://questiondoctors.com/i-have-a-burning-pain-in-pelvic-lower-abdomen-intestines/"
  },
  {
    "answer": "hi you should do a urine analysis and have a kidney ultrasound done if all is okay then it is probably pelvic inflammatory disease diet adjustment will be needed along with changing habits like avoid food containing wheat and go to the wc as soon as you feel like it with no delay good luck",
    "answer_author": "Dr Ahmed Fawzy",
    "question": "i have a burning pain in pelvic lower abdomen & intestines?",
    "question_text": "I have a burning pain in pelvic, lower abdomen & intestines?",
    "tags": [
      "lower abdomen"
    ],
    "url": "https://questiondoctors.com/i-have-a-burning-pain-in-pelvic-lower-abdomen-intestines/"
  },
  {
    "answer": "hi these are common side effects of lexapro lamictal and ambilify so you need to revise with your doctor for changing the drug or dose modification.",
    "answer_author": "Dr. Ayman Darrag",
    "question": "i had energy supplements now feeling dizzy and passed out today?",
    "question_text": "I had energy supplements  now feeling dizzy and passed out today?",
    "tags": [
      "energy supplements"
    ],
    "url": "https://questiondoctors.com/i-had-energy-supplements-now-feeling-dizzy-and-passed-out-today/"
  },
  {
    "answer": "hi this will pass avoid drinking alcohol with energy supplements in the future good luck",
    "answer_author": "Dr Ahmed Fawzy",
    "question": "i had energy supplements now feeling dizzy and passed out today?",
    "question_text": "I had energy supplements  now feeling dizzy and passed out today?",
    "tags": [
      "energy supplements"
    ],
    "url": "https://questiondoctors.com/i-had-energy-supplements-now-feeling-dizzy-and-passed-out-today/"
  },
  {
    "answer": "i laboratory check up is v imp yes it\u2019s v common side effects with the medication s your are taking but i need to do cbc \u060c check your blood pressure sitting and standing. .",
    "answer_author": "Dr Masr",
    "question": "i had energy supplements now feeling dizzy and passed out today?",
    "question_text": "I had energy supplements  now feeling dizzy and passed out today?",
    "tags": [
      "energy supplements"
    ],
    "url": "https://questiondoctors.com/i-had-energy-supplements-now-feeling-dizzy-and-passed-out-today/"
  },
  {
    "answer": "yes start letting it air dry but keep it clean and apply antiseptic ointment over it to. prevent infection. it will help in healing faster. hope this helps.",
    "answer_author": "Dr.Honey",
    "question": "i sliced the corner tip of my index finger off?",
    "question_text": "I sliced the corner tip of my index finger off?",
    "tags": [
      "finger is slowly healing"
    ],
    "url": "https://questiondoctors.com/i-sliced-the-corner-tip-of-my-index-finger-off/"
  },
  {
    "answer": "all of these consequences can occur but not necessarily all of them so peritonitis can occur in few hours to few days and sepsis can take few days to weeks depending on the case and when surgical inerference has happened after ruptured appendix. any further soecific question you are welcome to ask.",
    "answer_author": "Dr. Ayman Darrag",
    "question": "if an appendix ruptures how long would it take for sepsis to occur due to peritonitis?",
    "question_text": "If an appendix ruptures, how long would it take for sepsis to occur due to  peritonitis?",
    "tags": [
      "if an appendix ruptures"
    ],
    "url": "https://questiondoctors.com/if-an-appendix-ruptures-how-long-would-it-take-for-sepsis-to-occur-due-to-peritonitis/"
  },
  {
    "answer": "hi within first few hours peritonitis occur if drainage is applied early patient can be saved with good course of antibiotics kidney failure and sepsis depends on type of infection and put formation can not give u an accurate estimation but we are taking mainly days if no help received and weeks to month if care is given (may not happen with good care and a non resistant infection) good luck",
    "answer_author": "Dr Ahmed Fawzy",
    "question": "if an appendix ruptures how long would it take for sepsis to occur due to peritonitis?",
    "question_text": "If an appendix ruptures, how long would it take for sepsis to occur due to  peritonitis?",
    "tags": [
      "if an appendix ruptures"
    ],
    "url": "https://questiondoctors.com/if-an-appendix-ruptures-how-long-would-it-take-for-sepsis-to-occur-due-to-peritonitis/"
  },
  {
    "answer": "hours most probably but never days once peritonitis occur it\u2019s a life threatening condition",
    "answer_author": "Dr Masr",
    "question": "if an appendix ruptures how long would it take for sepsis to occur due to peritonitis?",
    "question_text": "If an appendix ruptures, how long would it take for sepsis to occur due to  peritonitis?",
    "tags": [
      "if an appendix ruptures"
    ],
    "url": "https://questiondoctors.com/if-an-appendix-ruptures-how-long-would-it-take-for-sepsis-to-occur-due-to-peritonitis/"
  },
  {
    "answer": "well peritonitis can cause rapid spread of infection if it is severe and can lead to multiple organ failure. so it is better to avoid delay and consult a physician or gastroenterologist and get evaluated. immediate medical and surgical intervention is a must. hope this helps",
    "answer_author": "Dr.Honey",
    "question": "if an appendix ruptures how long would it take for sepsis to occur due to peritonitis?",
    "question_text": "If an appendix ruptures, how long would it take for sepsis to occur due to  peritonitis?",
    "tags": [
      "if an appendix ruptures"
    ],
    "url": "https://questiondoctors.com/if-an-appendix-ruptures-how-long-would-it-take-for-sepsis-to-occur-due-to-peritonitis/"
  },
  {
    "answer": "hi you are on the right meds except for the propranolol dose which may need to be readjusted you are experiencing side effects of propranolol mainly also the medication choice is not typical to anxiety patients (unless you get lots of panic attacks then your doctor made the right choice) good luck",
    "answer_author": "Dr Ahmed Fawzy",
    "question": "i am a 20 male and i have been diagnosed with depression and anxiety am i taking the wrong meds?",
    "question_text": "I am a 20 male and I have been diagnosed with depression and anxiety, am I taking the wrong Meds?",
    "tags": [
      "am i taking the wrong meds"
    ],
    "url": "https://questiondoctors.com/i-am-a-20-male-and-i-have-been-diagnosed-with-depression-and-anxiety-am-i-taking-the-wrong-meds/"
  },
  {
    "answer": "u have done thyroid profile? +medical therapy is not going to be useful alone are u taking any psychological therapy? can i describe your symptoms more in order to help you",
    "answer_author": "Dr Masr",
    "question": "i am a 20 male and i have been diagnosed with depression and anxiety am i taking the wrong meds?",
    "question_text": "I am a 20 male and I have been diagnosed with depression and anxiety, am I taking the wrong Meds?",
    "tags": [
      "am i taking the wrong meds"
    ],
    "url": "https://questiondoctors.com/i-am-a-20-male-and-i-have-been-diagnosed-with-depression-and-anxiety-am-i-taking-the-wrong-meds/"
  }
]}